Connecticut Citizens Action Group Records 1987.0024
Archives and Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Library
- Series X: Mary Mushinsky Files, undated, 1973-1979
  - Town Planning, 1973 (Box 60:, Folder 2287)
  - 208 Planning, 1973 (Box 60:, Folder 2288)
  - 208 Policy Advisory Committee, 1978-1979 (Box 60:, Folder 2289-2291)
  - Unions (Box 60:, Folder 2292)
  - Utilities (Box 60:, Folder 2293)
  - Windsor Locks: Park and Airport Noise, 1978 (Box 60:, Folder 2294)
- Series XI: Environmental Issues, undated, 1971-1985
  - Air Pollution
    - Acid Rain (Box 61:, Folder 2295)
    - Air Quality Maintenance (Box 61:, Folder 2296-2298)
    - Air Quality Standards (Box 61:, Folder 2299)
    - Automobiles (Box 61:, Folder 2300-2302)
    - Clean Air Act (Box 61:, Folder 2303)
    - Clean Air Coalition (Box 61:, Folder 2304)
    - Coal Conservation, 1977 (Box 61:, Folder 2305)
    - CT's Air Quality Implementation Plan (Box 61:, Folder 2306-2307)
    - CT Business and Industry Association Lawsuit, 1979 (Box 61:, Folder 2308)
    - CCAG Funding Request Proposals (Box 61:, Folder 2309)
    - CT Clean Air Commission (Box 61:, Folder 2310)
    - CT Clean Air Plan, Implementation of (Box 61:, Folder 2311)
    - CT Department of Environmental Protection Civil Penalties, 1974 (Box 61:, Folder 2312)
    - CT Interagency Council on Smoking (Box 61:, Folder 2313)
    - CT News (Box 61:, Folder 2314)
    - CT Department of Environmental Protection (Box 61:, Folder 2315)
    - Fact Sheet (Box 61:, Folder 2316)
    - General Information (Box 61:, Folder 2317-2318)
    - Health Effects (Box 61:, Folder 2319-2320)
    - High Sulfur Fuels (Box 61:, Folder 2321-2323)
    - Implementation of Minnesota Clean Air Plan (Box 61:, Folder 2324)
    - Indirect Source of Air Pollution (Box 61:, Folder 2325-2330)
    - Indirect Source of Air Pollution (Box 62:, Folder 2331-2333)
    - Inspection and Maintenance (Box 62:, Folder 2334-2336)
    - Legislation (Box 62:, Folder 2337)
    - Moodus Conference (Box 62:, Folder 2338)
    - Pesticides (Box 62:, Folder 2339-2340)
    - Pollution Abatement Equipment (Box 62:, Folder 2341)
    - Prohibition (Box 62:, Folder 2342)
    - Project on Clean Air (Box 62:, Folder 2343-2344)
    - Publications (Box 62:, Folder 2345-2346)
    - Smoking (Box 62:, Folder 2347)
    - StanChem Affidavits (Box 62:, Folder 2348)
    - Sulfur (Box 62:, Folder 2349)
    - Toxic Air Pollutants (Box 62:, Folder 2350)
    - United Auto Workers and Emission Controls (Box 62:, Folder 2351)
    - Variance for High Sulfur Fuels (Box 62:, Folder 2352)
    - Various Topics (Box 62:, Folder 2353)
  - Conservation
    - Land Use (Box 62:, Folder 2354-2358)
    - Open Space (Box 62:, Folder 2359)
    - Wildlife (Box 62:, Folder 2360-2361)
    - Visual Pollution (Box 62:, Folder 2362)
    - East Hartford CAG (Box 62:, Folder 2363)
    - Eastern CT CAG (Box 62:, Folder 2364-2365)
  - Energy
    - Actions (Box 62:, Folder 2366)
    - Ad Book, 1984 (Box 62:, Folder 2367)
    - Ad Book, 1985 (Box 62:, Folder 2368)
    - Citizen/Labor Energy Coalition (CLEC) (Box 63:, Folder 2369-2380)
    - Citizens Utility Board (Box 63:, Folder 2381)
    - Co-generation (Box 63:, Folder 2382)
    - CT Legislature (Box 63:, Folder 2383)
    - Contacts (Box 63:, Folder 2384)
    - Department of Public Utility Control (DPUC) (Box 63:, Folder 2385-2387)
    - Editorial Fact Sheet on Electric Companies (Box 63:, Folder 2388)
    - Energy, 1983 (Box 63:, Folder 2389)
    - Energy, 1984 (Box 63:, Folder 2390)
    - Energy Assistance Information on Shut-offs (Box 63:, Folder 2391)
    - Energy Conservation Bulletin (Box 63:, Folder 2392)
    - Energy Deregulation (Box 63:, Folder 2393)
    - Energy Facts (Box 63:, Folder 2394)
    - Energy Facts, 1982 (Box 63:, Folder 2395)
    - Energy Facts, 1983 (Box 63:, Folder 2396)
    - Energy Management (Box 63:, Folder 2397)
    - Energy and Transportation Issues Committee (Box 63:, Folder 2398-2400)
    - Fact Sheet, Various (Box 64:, Folder 2401)
    - Flyer Originals (Box 64:, Folder 2402)
    - Fiscal Assistance (Box 64:, Folder 2403)
    - Gas Company (Box 64:, Folder 2404)
    - Gas Deregulation (Box 64:, Folder 2405-2406)
    - General Information (Box 64:, Folder 2407)
    - Health Care (Box 64:, Folder 2408)
    - Legislation, 1981 (Box 64:, Folder 2409)
    - Legislation, 1982 (Box 64:, Folder 2410)
    - Legislative Electoral Action Program (Box 64:, Folder 2411)
    - Legislative Index, 1984 (Box 64:, Folder 2412)
    - Legislative Session, 1983 (Box 64:, Folder 2413)
    - Letters to CCAG (Box 64:, Folder 2414)
    - Lobby Day, 1985 (Box 64:, Folder 2415)
    - Natural Gas Citizen/Labor Energy Coalition (Box 64:, Folder 2416)
    - Northeast Utilities Conservation (Box 64:, Folder 2417)
    - Northeast Utilities Shareholders Letter (Box 64:, Folder 2418)
    - Nuclear Energy (Box 64:, Folder 2419)
    - Oil Companies (Box 64:, Folder 2420)
    - Press Labels (Box 64:, Folder 2421)
    - Rate Witholding Cammpaign (Box 64:, Folder 2422)
  - Environmental Protection
    - General (Box 64:, Folder 2423-2425)
  - Fuels
    - CT National Gas (Box 64:, Folder 2426)
    - Estimated Billing Campaign (Box 64:, Folder 2427)
    - Fuel Adjustment (Box 64:, Folder 2428)
    - Northeast Utilities (Box 64:, Folder 2429-2430)
    - Nuclear Power (Box 64:, Folder 2431-2432)
    - Power Facility Evaluation Council, 1977 (Box 64:, Folder 2433-2434)
    - Radioactive Waste (Box 64:, Folder 2435)
    - Rate Structure (Box 64:, Folder 2436)
    - Solar (Box 64:, Folder 2437-2438)
    - Southern CT Gas (Box 64:, Folder 2439-2440)
    - SNET (Box 64:, Folder 2441)
    - Utility Press Clippings (Box 64:, Folder 2442)
  - General
    - Affirmative Action (Box 64:, Folder 2443)
    - Army Crops of Engineers (Box 64:, Folder 2444)
    - Canvassing (Box 64:, Folder 2445)
    - Cleveland UAW (Box 65:, Folder 2446)
    - Coalition for Consumer Justice (Box 65:, Folder 2447)
    - Community Services (Box 65:, Folder 2448)
    - CT Action Now (Box 65:, Folder 2449)
    - CCAG Policies (Box 65:, Folder 2450)
    - CCAG Publications (Box 65:, Folder 2451)
    - CT Health Department (Box 65:, Folder 2452)
    - CT UAW Convention, 1977 (Box 65:, Folder 2453)
    - Consumer Action Now (Box 65:, Folder 2454)
    - Council on Environmental Quality (Box 65:, Folder 2455)
    - Demographics and Planning (Box 65:, Folder 2456)
    - Department of Energy (Box 65:, Folder 2457-2458)
    - Department of Interior Bibliography (Box 65:, Folder 2459)
    - Department of Environmental Protection, CT (Box 65:, Folder 2460)
    - Direct Action Organizing (Box 65:, Folder 2461-2462)
    - Earth Day, 1980 (Box 65:, Folder 2463)
    - Economy (Box 65:, Folder 2464)
    - Energy Coalition (Box 65:, Folder 2465)
    - Environmental Brag Sheet, CCAG (Box 65:, Folder 2466)
    - Environmental Caucus (Box 65:, Folder 2467-2468)
    - Environmental Groups (Box 65:, Folder 2469-2470)
    - Environmental Philosophy/Ethics (Box 65:, Folder 2471)
    - Environmental Protection Action Committee (Box 65:, Folder 2472)
    - Environmental Protection Agency (Box 65:, Folder 2473-2475)
    - Environmental Workplan, Events, Conferences (Box 65:, Folder 2476)
    - Future Organizing (Box 65:, Folder 2477)
    - Governor's Committee to Develop an Environmental Policy for Connecticut (Box 65:, Folder 2478)
    - Gypsy Moth (Box 65:, Folder 2479)
    - Impact Statements (Box 65:, Folder 2480-2481)
    - Incorporation (Box 65:, Folder 2482)
    - Jobs and Environment (Box 65:, Folder 2483-2484)
    - Legislative Achievements, 1978 (Box 65:, Folder 2485)
    - Legislative Achievements, 1979 (Box 65:, Folder 2486)
    - Lobbying (Box 65:, Folder 2487)
    - Meriden (Box 65:, Folder 2488)
    - Meskill Bibliography (Box 65:, Folder 2489)
    - Midwest Academy (Box 65:, Folder 2490-2491)
    - National Energy Coalition (Box 65:, Folder 2492)
    - New Haven Water Company (Box 66:, Folder 2493)
    - Newington (Box 66:, Folder 2494)
    - New Roots (Box 66:, Folder 2495)
    - Newsletter (Box 66:, Folder 2496)
    - North Hartford (Box 66:, Folder 2497)
    - Norwich (Box 66:, Folder 2498-2499)
    - Nuclear Energy (Box 66:, Folder 2500)
    - Occupational Safety (Box 66:, Folder 2501)
    - Oil (Box 66:, Folder 2502-2504)
    - Organizing (Box 66:, Folder 2505-2506)
    - Organizing Training (Box 66:, Folder 2507)
    - Other Chapters (Box 66:, Folder 2508)
    - People's Bicentennial Commission (Box 66:, Folder 2509)
    - Personal Press Testimony (Box 66:, Folder 2510)
    - Policy Statements (Box 66:, Folder 2511)
    - Positive Paper: Solar (Box 66:, Folder 2512)
    - Professional Drivers (Box 66:, Folder 2513)
    - Public Participation (Box 66:, Folder 2514)
    - Puerto Rican Center for Justice (Box 66:, Folder 2515)
    - Radiation (Box 66:, Folder 2516)
    - Radio Spots (Box 66:, Folder 2517)
    - Reagan Environmental Record, Case Against (Box 66:, Folder 2518)
    - Recycling) (Box 66:, Folder 2519-2527)
    - Regional Energy Program (Box 66:, Folder 2528)
    - Stamford (Box 67:, Folder 2529)
    - Survival Kit (Box 67:, Folder 2530)
    - Testimony, 1979 (Box 67:, Folder 2531)
    - Tufts University (Box 67:, Folder 2532)
    - Urban Environment (Box 67:, Folder 2533-2537)
    - Virginia Citizen's Consumer Council (Box 67:, Folder 2538)
    - Waste (Box 67:, Folder 2539-2543)
    - Waterbury (Box 67:, Folder 2544)
    - Yale and Harvard Research (Box 67:, Folder 2545)
  - Hazardous Waste
    - Area-wide Waste Treatment Management Planning Board (Box 67:, Folder 2546)
    - Berlin (Box 67:, Folder 2547)
    - Congressman Moffett's Hazardous Waste Task Force (Box 67:, Folder 2548)
    - CT Council for Occupational Safety and Health (COSH) (Box 67:, Folder 2549-2550)
    - CT Incidents (Box 67:, Folder 2551-02552)
    - Contamination (Box 67:, Folder 2553-2555)
    - Department of Environmental Protection (Box 67:, Folder 2556-2557)
    - Environmental Mediation Center (Box 67:, Folder 2558)
    - Fact Sheet (Box 67:, Folder 2559)
    - General Information (Box 67:, Folder 2560)
    - Hazardous Waste Committee (Box 67:, Folder 2561-2565)
    - Industrial Waste Task Force (Box 67:, Folder 2566-2568)
    - Kement Landfill (Box 67:, Folder 2569)
    - Lobby Day, 1982 (Box 68:, Folder 2570)
    - National Campaigns Against Toxic Waste, CT Contact list (Box 68:, Folder 2571)
    - National Campaigns Against Toxic Hazards (Box 68:, Folder 2572-2573)
    - National Groups (Box 68:, Folder 2574)
    - National Landfills, Dumps (Box 68:, Folder 2575)
    - Other Organizations (Box 68:, Folder 2576)
    - PCB's (Box 68:, Folder 2577)
    - Resource Conservation and Recovery Act (Box 68:, Folder 2578)
    - Right to Know (Box 68:, Folder 2579-2581)
    - Shelton Landfill (Box 68:, Folder 2582)
    - Southington Solvents Recovery (Box 68:, Folder 2583)
    - Summary and Definitions (Box 68:, Folder 2584)
    - Superfund (Box 68:, Folder 2585)
    - Surcharge Act (Box 68:, Folder 2586)
    - Surcharge Amendment (Box 68:, Folder 2587)
    - Technical Assistance (Box 68:, Folder 2588-2589)
    - Toby Moffett's Hazardous Waste Task Force (Box 68:, Folder 2590)
    - Toxic Air (Box 68:, Folder 2591)
    - Trash and Energy (Box 68:, Folder 2592)
    - Various Information (Box 68:, Folder 2593)
  - Housing
    - Committee Meetings (Box 68:, Folder 2594)
    - Council on Alternative State and Local Policies (Box 68:, Folder 2595)
    - Developments, 1983-1987 (Box 68:, Folder 2596)
    - Fact Sheets and Flyers (Box 68:, Folder 2597)
    - Housing, 1982 (Box 68:, Folder 2589)
    - Housing, 1983 (Box 68:, Folder 2599)
    - Just Cause Eviction, 1983-1984 (Box 68:, Folder 2600)
    - Legislation, 1983 (Box 68:, Folder 2601)
    - Legislation, 1985 (Box 68:, Folder 2602)
    - Other States (Box 68:, Folder 2603)
    - Rent Control (Box 68:, Folder 2604-2606)
    - Research (Box 69:, Folder 2607)
    - Statewide Tenants (Box 69:, Folder 2608)
    - Tenants Rights Month (Box 69:, Folder 2609)
  - Legislation
    - Bills Introduced, 1971 (Box 69:, Folder 2610)
    - Bills Introduced, 1972 (Box 69:, Folder 2611)
    - Bills, CT (Box 69:, Folder 2612)
    - Bottle Bill, 1977 (Box 69:, Folder 2613)
    - Bottle Bill, 1979 (Box 69:, Folder 2614)
    - Bottle Bill, 1980 (Box 69:, Folder 2615)
    - Citizen Participation in CT Land Use (Box 69:, Folder 2616)
    - Commission on Environmental Protection and Economic Development (DEPED), 1978 (Box 69:, Folder 2617-2618)
    - CCAG Legislative Package, 1979 (Box 69:, Folder 2619)
    - CT Environmental Policy Act (CEPA) (Box 69:, Folder 2620-2628)
    - CT UAWCAP Legislation (Box 69:, Folder 2629)
    - Consumer Legislation, 1979 (Box 69:, Folder 2630)
    - Correspondence, 1979 (Box 69:, Folder 2631)
    - Council on Environmental Quality (Box 69:, Folder 2632-2633)
    - Department of Environmental Protection Bill, 1979 (Box 69:, Folder 2634)
    - Department of Environmental Protection, CT (Box 69:, Folder 2635-2636)
    - Description and Evaluation of CT Bills, 1971 (Box 69:, Folder 2637)
    - Description and Evaluation of CT Bills, 1972 (Box 69:, Folder 2638)
    - Direct Approach to S.C. #113 (Box 69:, Folder 2639)
    - Economics of Pollution Abatement/Costs/Benefits (Box 70:, Folder 2640)
    - Election Results and Legislative Addresses, 1978 (Box 70:, Folder 2641)
    - Environment Committee (Box 70:, Folder 2642-2645)
    - Environment: Miscellaneous (Box 70:, Folder 2646)
    - Environmental Policy Act, CT (Box 70:, Folder 2647)
    - Environmental Protection Act, 1971 (Box 70:, Folder 2648)
    - Executive Order 16, 1972 (Box 70:, Folder 2649)
    - General, Federal (Box 70:, Folder 2650)
    - Hearing Transcripts and Copies of Wetlands Bills (Box 70:, Folder 2651)
    - Inland Wetlands (Box 70:, Folder 2652)
    - Land Use Policy Act, Federal (Box 70:, Folder 2653)
    - Legislative Information, 1977 (Box 70:, Folder 2654)
    - Manchester Environmental Coalition v. Stockton CEOA Case, 1977 (Box 70:, Folder 2655)
    - Pac, Stanley (with cassette tape of Pac/Caplan) (Box 70:, Folder 2656)
    - Pesticides (Box 70:, Folder 2657)
    - Schneidermeyer, Melvin (Box 70:, Folder 2658)
    - Publications (Box 70:, Folder 2659)
    - Solar Energy in Planning and Zoning (Box 70:, Folder 2660)
    - Water (Box 70:, Folder 2661-2662)
  - Noise
    - General (Box 70:, Folder 2663-2666)
  - Planning
    - General (Box 70:, Folder 2667-2670)
  - Water
    - Attorney General's Actions (Box 70:, Folder 2671)
    - Berlin, CT (Box 70:, Folder 2672-2678)
    - Bethel, CT (Box 70:, Folder 2679)
    - Coastal Wetlands (Box 70:, Folder 2680)
    - CT Inland Wetland Project (Box 71:, Folder 2681)
    - Connecticut River (Box 71:, Folder 2682)
    - Department of Environmental Protection (Box 71:, Folder 2683)
    - Dredging (Box 71:, Folder 2684)
    - Drinking Water (Box 71:, Folder 2685-2687)
    - Enforcement, Federal and State (Box 71:, Folder 2688)
    - Environmental Protection Agency (Box 71:, Folder 2689-2690)
    - Fact Sheets: StanChem (Box 71:, Folder 2691)
    - Fish Kills (Box 71:, Folder 2692)
    - Floods (Box 71:, Folder 2693-2694)
    - Freedom of Information (Box 71:, Folder 2695-2696)
    - General Information (Box 71:, Folder 2697-2698)
    - Harbor (Box 71:, Folder 2699)
    - Housatonic Valley Association (Box 71:, Folder 2700)
    - Industrial Wastes (Box 71:, Folder 2701)
    - Inland Wetlands (Box 71:, Folder 2702)
    - Long Island Sound) (Box 71:, Folder 2703-2704)
    - Monitoring Drinking Water (Box 71:, Folder 2705)
    - National Pollutant Discharge Elimination System (NPDES) (Box 71:, Folder 2706)
    - New England River Basins Commission (NERBC) (Box 71:, Folder 2707-2709)
    - Oil Spills (Box 71:, Folder 2710-2712)
    - Phosphates (Box 71:, Folder 2713-2714)
    - Rivers, CT (Box 71:, Folder 2715)
    - River Basin Studies (Box 71:, Folder 2716)
    - Rykar Case (Box 71:, Folder 2717)
    - Shelton Landfill (Box 71:, Folder 2718-2725)
    - StanChem (Box 72:, Folder 2726-2735)
    - Tidal Wetlands (Box 73:, Folder 2736-2739)
    - Water Company Lands, 1977 (Box 73:, Folder 2740)
    - Water Publications (Box 73:, Folder 2741)
    - Water Quality (Box 73:, Folder 2742-2745)
    - Water Regulations (Box 73:, Folder 2746-2747)
    - Water Safety (Box 73:, Folder 2748)
  - Julie Mannarino Files
    - Acid Rain, 1977 (Box 74:, Folder 2749)
    - Air Compliance Engineering, 1974 (Box 74:, Folder 2750)
    - Air Conservation Committee, 1975-1977 (Box 74:, Folder 2751)
    - Air Conservation Legislation, 1977 (Box 74:, Folder 2752)
    - Air Pollution Publication (Box 74:, Folder 2753)
    - Alternate Transportation Plan (Box 74:, Folder 2754)
    - "Bust the Highway Trust", 1975-1977 (Box 74:, Folder 2755)
    - Chess Study, 1977 (Box 74:, Folder 2756)
    - Chieppo Bus Company, 1979 (Box 74:, Folder 2757)
    - Citizen Government Transportation Planning Center, 1975-1979 (Box 74:, Folder 2758-2759)
    - Citizens Task Force on Mass Transportation, 1975 (Box 74:, Folder 2760)
    - CCAG Legislation, 1978 (Box 74:, Folder 2761)
    - CT Continuing Committee on State Planning and Development (Box 74:, Folder 2762)
    - CT Department of Environmental Protection: Airborne Sulfates (Box 74:, Folder 2763)
    - CT Transit, 1978-1979 (Box 74:, Folder 2764)
    - CT Transportation Control Plan (Box 74:, Folder 2765-2766)
    - Department of Environmental Protection Reports, 1975-1977 (Box 74:, Folder 2767)
    - Department of Transportation: Federal Planning Regulations (Box 74:, Folder 2768)
    - Department of Transportation: Press Releases (Box 74:, Folder 2769)
    - Emission Test Reports: United Illuminating (Box 74:, Folder 2770-2775)
    - Environmental Statement: I-91/I-291 (Box 75:, Folder 2776)
      - Maps (Box 75:, Folder 2777)
    - Federal Highway Administration (Box 75:, Folder 2778)
    - Highway Construction Costs (Box 75:, Folder 2779)
    - Interstate 84, Eastern Connecticut
      - I-84 (Box 75:, Folder 2780-2784)
      - Ads Against (Box 75:, Folder 2785)
      - CCAG Information (Box 75:, Folder 2786)
      - CT Construction Industries Assoc. (Box 75:, Folder 2787)
      - Connector Road: I-85/I-86 (Box 75:, Folder 2788)
      - Correspondence with National Groups (Box 75:, Folder 2789)
      - Council on Environmental Quality (Box 75:, Folder 2790)
      - Effects on Jobs in Eastern Connecticut (Box 75:, Folder 2791)
      - Environmental Issues Status (Box 75:, Folder 2792)
      - General (Box 75:, Folder 2793-2794)
      - Impact Study (Box 75:, Folder 2795)
      - Legal Briefs (Box 75:, Folder 2796)
      - Litigation (Box 75:, Folder 2797)
      - News Releases (Box 75:, Folder 2798)
      - Overview Assessment (Box 75:, Folder 2799)
      - R.I. Environmental Impact Study (Box 75:, Folder 2800)
      - Rubin, Judith (Box 75:, Folder 2801)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 76:, Folder 2802-2806)
    - Powers, Arthur: DOT Commissioner (Box 76:, Folder 2807)
    - Proposed Transportation Control Plan (Box 76:, Folder 2808)
    - Research Corporation Studies: Sulfur Dioxide Concentrations (Box 76:, Folder 2809)
    - Secondary Standards (Box 76:, Folder 2810)
    - Solar Energy (Box 76:, Folder 2811)
    - Statewide Air Pollution Research Center (Box 76:, Folder 2812)
    - Sulfates, 1975 (Box 76:, Folder 2813)
    - Sulfur Briefs, 1976 (Box 76:, Folder 2814)
    - Sulfur: Correspondence, 1976 (Box 76:, Folder 2815)
    - Sulfur Scrubbing Study, 1977 (Box 76:, Folder 2816)
    - Sulfur Transcripts (Box 76:, Folder 2817)
    - Sulfur Variances and Hearings, 1976 (Box 76:, Folder 2818)
    - Traffic, 1976 (Box 76:, Folder 2819)
    - Transportation Control Plan (Box 77:, Folder 2820)
    - Transportation Funding (Box 77:, Folder 2821)
    - Urban Policy (Box 77:, Folder 2822)
    - Utility DEP Studies, 1975 (Box 77:, Folder 2823)
    - Utility Testimony: High Sulfer Fuels (Box 77:, Folder 2824)
  - unspecified
    For further information on this subject, see: Series I: Director's Records, Marc Caplan Files, Miles Rappoport Files, Lenny Norwitz Files, and Scott Hempling Files; Series III: Administrative Files; Series IX: Bottle Bill; Series X: Mary Mushinky Files; Series XVI: Subject Files; and Series XVII: 1992 Addendum.
- Series XII: Energy Issues, undated, 1964-1982
  - National
    - Air Conditioning, Refrigeration (Box 78:, Folder 2825)
    - Alternate Energy Sources (Box 78:, Folder 2826)
    - Alternative Energy, 1978 (Box 78:, Folder 2827-2828)
    - Appropriate Technology Network Conference, 1977 (Box 78:, Folder 2829)
    - Arctic Gas Project, 1977 (Box 78:, Folder 2830)
    - Armory Lovins, 1978 (Box 78:, Folder 2831)
    - Automobile Economy Standards (Box 78:, Folder 2832)
    - Automobile Fuel Economy Legislation (Box 78:, Folder 2833)
    - Building Insulation (Box 78:, Folder 2834)
    - California (Box 78:, Folder 2835)
    - California Energy Bill, 1973 (Box 78:, Folder 2836)
    - California Office of Appropriate Technology, 1976 (Box 78:, Folder 2837)
    - Carter's Energy Policy, 1977 (Box 78:, Folder 2838)
    - Community Energy Planning, 1976-1977 (Box 78:, Folder 2839)
    - Community Energy Conservation (Box 78:, Folder 2840)
    - Conservation, 1974-1977 (Box 78:, Folder 2841-2843)
    - Decontrol Data (Box 78:, Folder 2844)
    - Department of the Treasury, 1973 (Box 78:, Folder 2845-2846)
    - Economic Growth and Electric Power, 1972-1973 (Box 78:, Folder 2847)
    - Electricity and the Environment, 1973 (Box 78:, Folder 2848-2849)
    - Emergency Fuel Aid Program, 1978 (Box 78:, Folder 2850)
    - Energy
      - Ford Program (Box 78:, Folder 2851)
      - Newsletters, Notes, Testimony, Correspondence, 1974-1975 (Box 78:, Folder 2852)
      - Other States/Countries (Box 78:, Folder 2853)
    - Energy Bills, 1973 (Box 79:, Folder 2854)
    - Energy Conservation
      - Aids (Box 79:, Folder 2855)
      - Economic Growth (Box 79:, Folder 2856)
      - Electricity (Box 79:, Folder 2857)
      - Federal Government (Box 79:, Folder 2858)
      - General Need (Box 79:, Folder 2859)
      - General Solutions (Box 79:, Folder 2860)
      - Industrial (Box 79:, Folder 2861)
      - Jobs (Box 79:, Folder 2862)
      - Other States (Box 79:, Folder 2863)
      - Plans, Other States, 1976-1978 (Box 79:, Folder 2864)
      - Production (Box 79:, Folder 2865)
      - Residential (Box 79:, Folder 2866)
      - Transportation (Box 79:, Folder 2867)
      - Utilities (Box 79:, Folder 2868-2869)
    - Energy Crisis, 1972-1973 (Box 79:, Folder 2870-2871)
    - Energy Legislation, 1969-1973 (Box 79:, Folder 2872-2874)
    - Energy Policy Projects, 1972 (Box 79:, Folder 2875)
    - Energy Prices and Alternative Energy Policies (Box 79:, Folder 2876)
    - Energy Production (Box 79:, Folder 2877-2878)
    - Energy Research Legislation, 1972 (Box 79:, Folder 2879)
    - Energy Testimony, 1974-1975 (Box 79:, Folder 2880)
    - Environmental Impact, 1970 (Box 79:, Folder 2881)
    - Environmental Legislation (Box 79:, Folder 2882)
    - Environmental Organization, 1977 (Box 79:, Folder 2883)
    - EPA Workshop (Box 79:, Folder 2884)
    - Federal Energy Policy, 1975 (Box 79:, Folder 2885)
    - Federal Energy Regulations, 1978 (Box 79:, Folder 2886)
    - Federal Power Commission, 1972-1973 (Box 79:, Folder 2887)
    - Fossil/Synthetic Fuels (Box 79:, Folder 2888)
    - Fuel Employment Coalition, 1977-78 (Box 79:, Folder 2889-2890)
    - Fusion Power (Box 79:, Folder 2891)
    - Gas Pipeline, 1978 (Box 79:, Folder 2892)
    - Gasoline, 1979 (Box 79:, Folder 2893)
    - Geothermal Power (Box 79:, Folder 2894)
    - Hazardous Waste (Box 79:, Folder 2895-2896)
    - Hydroelectric Power (Box 79:, Folder 2897)
    - Industry: General Information (Box 79:, Folder 2898)
    - Industry Newsletters (Box 79:, Folder 2899)
    - Load Control (Box 79:, Folder 2900)
    - Massachusetts (Box 79:, Folder 2901)